var questions = [
	{
		question: "Whats is the Full-Form Of HTML?",
		opt: ["hyper text machine language","high tech machine language","hyper text markup language","high text markup language"],
		ans: "hyper text markup language"
	},
	{
		question: "Who is the father of python?",
		opt: ["Brenden Eich","Guido van Rossum","bjarne strousstrup","charless babbage"],
		ans: "Guido van Rossum"
	},
	{
		question: "How can you reverse a string in Python",
		opt: ["using StringBuffer","using def","using if else statement","using stringReverse"],
		ans: "using StringBuffer"
	},
	{
		question: "What will be the value x in this code\nlet x = 0;\nif(x < 1){\nx++\n}",
		opt: ["0","6","11","1"],
		ans: "1"
	},
	{
		question: "Translator which is used to convert codes of assembly language into machine language is termed as",
		opt: ["assembler","attempter","compiler","debugger"],
		ans: "assembler"
	},
	{
		question: "Higher-order functions are not built into the",
		opt: ["Python","structural language","JAVA","C++"],
		ans: "structural language"
	},
	{
		question: "Diagram which shows relationship between classes is termed as",
		opt: ["Class diagram","sequential diagram","use case diagram","communication diagram"],
		ans: "Class diagram"
	},
	{
		question: "Animation and interactivity with the user on web pages can be done by",
		opt: ["JavaScript","Python","Java","C#"],
		ans: "JavaScript"
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following language run on terminal?",
		opt: ["HTML","CSS","NodeJs","PHP"],
		ans: "NodeJs"
	},
	{
		question: "In Programming we call an erros as",
		opt: ["Bug","Problem","Erros","Insect"],
		ans: "Bug"
	},
	{
		question: "The language understood by a computer without translation is called",
		opt: ["High-level Language","Command Language","assembly language","Machine language"],
		ans: "Machine language"
	},
]
